Guide to the University of Pittsburgh Archives Personal Files, 1824-present UA.Personal.Files
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- R
  - Rodnan, Gerald P.
  - Rodnan, Joan
  - Roebuck, Anne *
  - Roeder, Richard W.
  - Roemele, Curt
  - Roethlisberger, Ben
  - Rogers, Clark D.
  - Rogers, David B.
  - Rogers, Jason
  - Rogers, Fred
  - Rogers, Joanne
  - Rogers, Kenneth
  - Rogers, Paul L.
  - Rogers, Robert M. *
  - Rogers, Robin
  - Roggiano, Alfredo (Dr.) *
  - Rogoff, Elizabeth (Dr.)
  - Rogoff, Julius
  - Rohan, Lisa
  - Rohm, Curtis Lee
  - Rohm, Theodore L.
  - Rohrbach, Quincy A. W.
  - Rohrbacher, Paul F.
  - Rohrer, Wesley
  - Rohrssen, Barry
  - Rojas, Cecilia
  - Roling, Jay H.
  - Rollins, Harold
  - Rollman, Sarah
  - Roman-Koller, Anna
  - Romani, John H. (Dr.)
  - Romano, Michael
  - Rombaut, Raoul
  - Romer, Roy
  - Romesberg, Daniel
  - Romett, Carol
  - Romkes, Marjorie
  - Romoff, Jeffrey
  - Ronchetti, Ann
  - Rondan, Nelson
  - Roodman, David
  - Rooney, Dan
  - Rooney, David
  - Rooney, James
  - Roosevelt, Mark
  - Root, Deane (oversize)
  - Root, William T. *
  - Rooths, Eunity
  - Rosanoff, H. A.
  - Rosborough, Mary Lou
  - Rosborough, Robert *
  - Roscoe, Rod
  - Rose, Andrew T.
  - Rose, Evans
  - Rose, Gloria *
  - Rose, Harold J.
  - Rose, Justin
  - Rose, M. Richard
  - Rose, Mike
  - Rose, Russell R.
  - Roselle, William C.
  - Ross, Madelyn A.
  - Rosell, Glenora Edwards
  - Roseman, Alvin *
  - Rosen, Clark A.
  - Rosen, Daniel
  - Rosen, James (Dr.)
  - Rosen, Jules
  - Rosen, Norwin A.
  - Rosen, Steven *
  - Rosenbaum, Jordon T.
  - Rosenberg, David
  - Rosenberg, David L.
  - Rosenberg, Heidi
  - Rosenberg, Jerome *
  - Rosenberg, John
  - Rosenberg, Reinhardt
  - Rosenberg, Stanford H.
  - Rosenbloom, Jacob
  - Rosenblum, Matthew
  - Rosenblum, Warren
  - Rosenkranz, Herbert
  - Rosenmeier, Mike
  - Rosenstiel, Sharon
  - Rosenthal, Theodore B.
  - Rosi, Nathan
  - Rosinski, Richard R.
  - Roskies, Ralph Z.
  - Rosner, Jerome (Dr.)
  - Rosnes, Renee
  - Rosol, Joanne, II
  - Rosomoff, Hubert L.
  - Ross, Alan O. *
  - Ross, Helen *
  - Ross, James *
  - Ross, James, Jr. *
  - Ross, Leslie
  - Ross, Madelyn A.
  - Ross, Phillip
  - Rossell, Glenora Edwards *
  - Ross-Franklin, Jean
  - Rossell, James
  - Rossetti, Guy
  - Rossman, Carl
  - Roth, Alvin
  - Roth, Cynthia
  - Roth, Leonard
  - Roth, Loren H.
  - Roth, Marvin
  - Roth, Ronald N.
  - Roth, Yogi
  - Rothenberg, Janet
  - Rothkrug, Lionel Nathan
  - Rothman, Irv *
  - Rothman, Jack *
  - Roublev, Michel
  - Rougeux, Debora
  - Rountree, B. C. *
  - Rountree, Lisa
  - Roux, Stanley Joseph
  - Rovansek, Ronald M.
  - Rovee, Ben
  - Rovelli, Carlo
  - Rowan, Frederick Johnson
  - Rowe, Stuart N.
  - Rowell, Henry T.
  - Rowland, Howard
  - Rowley, Sally (Mrs.)
  - Rowley, Sean
  - Roy, Donald E. *
  - Roy, Partha
  - Roydes, Rona L.
  - Royer, James E.
  - Ruane, Amanda
  - Ruane, Margaret
  - Ruark, Arthur E.
  - Rubash, Harry
  - Ruben, Frederick
  - Ruben, Jacob
  - Rubenstein, Farrell
  - Rubenstein, J. S.
  - Rubenstein, Linda
  - Rubenstein, Richard Lowell
  - Rubin, Allen *
  - Rubin, Daniel
  - Rubin, Emmanuel
  - Rubin, Harry
  - Rubin, Herbert
  - Rubin, Joshua T.
  - Rubin, Julius (Dr.)
  - Rubin, Reva
  - Rubin-Grandis, Jennifer
  - Rubinstein, Wendy
  - Ruch, Charles P.
  - Ruck, Rob
  - Rucker, Malaya
  - Rud, Kathleen A.
  - Rudisill, W. A.
  - Ruday, W. *
  - Rudwin, Maximilian J.
  - Rudy, Ellen Beam
  - Rudy, Thomas E.
  - Rued, William
  - Ruf, Edward L.
  - Ruffian, Cheryl
  - Ruggieri, Helen
  - Ruhe, C. H. William
  - Ruibal, Claudio
  - Ruiz, Cande
  - Rukavina, Bob
  - Rulin, Marvin C.
  - Rumick, Robert
  - Rune, William *
  - Rupert, F. F.
  - Rupp, Stanley
  - Rusesabagina, Paul
  - Rush, Helen *
  - Rush, Mark
  - Rush, Philip E.
  - Rushkowski, Corrine
  - Rusiewicz, Heather Leavy
  - Rusinow, Dennison
  - Rusk, David
  - Ruskin, Brian
  - Russ, Clem
  - Russell, Alan J.
  - Russell, Charles T.
  - Russell, Charles, Jr.
  - Russell, Richard L.
  - Russell, Roger W. (oversize) *
  - Russell, Thomas
  - Russo, Stephen A.
  - Rutan, Gale
  - Rutherford, Rod
  - Rutherford, Vanessa
  - Rutledge, Lee
  - Ruttenberg, Katherine M.
  - Ruvolo, Catherine
  - Ryan, Christopher
  - Ryan, Kathleen
  - Ryan, Neal
  - Ryan, Trisha
  - Rychek, Russell R.
  - Rykaceski, Stuart
  - Ryland, Gladys *
  - Ryndycz, Jessica
  - Rynearson, Edward
- S
  - Saalbach, Louis *
  - Saaty, Thomas L.
  - Saba, Robert
  - Sabean, David
  - Sabloff, Jeremy A.
  - Sack, Gerry Ruth
  - Sacks, Jerome Morris
  - Sacks, Louis
  - Sacks, Michael
  - Sacks, Patricia
  - Safar, Peter *
  - Saffer, Elizabeth
  - Safford, Hurd W. (Dr.)
  - Saffron, Jennifer Teresa
  - Sage, Evan Taylor *
  - Sage, Jack
  - Sahlin, James L.
  - Sailer, Lee
  - Sainsbury, Trevor (Dr.) *
  - St. Aubyn, Frederic Chase (Dr.)
  - Saint Denis, Gerald C.
  - St. John, David
  - St. John, Kate
  - St. Peter, Wilfred N. *
  - Sakmar, Joseph J. *
  - Salama, Guy
  - Salamun, Tomaz
  - Saleh, Ayman
  - Salem, Chuck
  - Saliba, George *
  - Salisbury, Ruth
  - Salk, Jonas
  - Salk, Jonas (Mrs.)
  - Salkovitz, Ed I. *
  - Sallad-Farina, Betsy
  - Salloum, Ihsan M.
  - Salmon, Wesley C. (Dr.)
  - Salper, Roberta *
  - Salter, Bryant
  - Salter, Russell
  - Salvatori, Mariolina
  - Salvin, S. B. *
  - Salyers, Samantha
  - Sammartino, Bruno (oversize)
  - Sample, William *
  - Samples, Jerry W.
  - Samuel, Irene
  - Samuelson, Pamela
  - Samulski, Richard Jude
  - Sanchez, Eduardo
  - Sanchez, Sonia
  - Sandberg, David
  - Sanders, Derrick
  - Sanders, Leon
  - Sanders, Patricia
  - Sanders, Paul H.
  - Sandler, Rivka B.
  - Sanfilippo, Joseph
  - Sanford, O'Neill
  - Sanft, Donna
  - Sankey, Harold H.
  - Sanielevici, Emil
  - Sankovsky, Raymond John
  - Santoro, Daniel
  - Santorum, Rick
  - Santucci, Francesco
  - Santucci, Vince
  - Sanz, Maria Teresa *
  - Saporta, Sol
  - Sarat, Austin
  - Sargent, Barbara
  - Sargent, George Q. *
  - Saris-Mechenbier, Lydia
  - Sarkar, Surojit
  - Sarles, Harvey (Dr.)
  - Sarma, D. S. R.
  - Sarnowski, Johanna
  - Sarri, Rosemary
  - Sartain, Harry *
  - Sassano, John J. *
  - Saouni, Viken
  - Sataloff, Matthew
  - Sauer, Johnny
  - Saunders, Allene Wallen
  - Saunders, Stephen
  - Saunders, Wilfred L.
  - Saunders, William
  - Saurer, Stella
  - Savage, A.
  - Savage, Kirk
  - Savage, Lawrence D.
  - Savage, William
  - Savich, Richard
  - Savin, Ovidiu
  - Savini, Carolyne
  - Savini, Tom
  - Savio, Lau-Yuen Woo
  - Savisky, Timothy
  - Savits, Thomas H.
  - Savoia, Francesca L.
  - Sawyer, Frederick W.
  - Sawyer, Helen Rae
  - Sawyer, Thomas J. (Rev.) *
  - Sax, Martin
  - Saxena, Sunil
  - Saxena, Sweta
  - Saxon, A. H.
  - Say, James B.
  - Saylor, Paul H.
  - Saylor, Tillman
  - Sbragia, Alberta
  - Scaglion, Richard
  - Scaife, Alan Magee *
  - Scaife, David
  - Scaife, Jennie
  - Scaife, Richard M.
  - Scaife, Sarah Mellon *
  - Scales, Alice M.
  - Scanlon, Eugene F.
  - Scanlon, Norman W.
  - Scantlebury, Velma Patricia
  - Scanzano, Mike
  - Schaal, Eric
  - Schade, Robert
  - Schaefer, Andrew
  - Schaefer, Halmuth
  - Schaefer, Kathleen
  - Schaefer, Laura
  - Schaeffer, Josephine O'Brien
  - Schaeffer, Marguerite *
  - Schaeffer, Wendell G. *
  - Schaffner, Ken
  - Schafmeister, Christian E.
  - Schano, John *
  - Scharfe, Howard C. (Dr.) *
  - Schatten, Gerald P.
  - Schatz, Tom
  - Schaub, Richard D.
  - Schauer, Philip
  - Scheirer, Mary Ann (Mrs.)
  - Schell, William
  - Schempp, Ellroy
  - Schenley, Mary
  - Scher, Mark S.
  - Schertz, Charles *
  - Schiff, David
  - Schiller, Michael
  - Schiff, Paul L.
  - Schindler, John T.
  - Schiros, Matt
  - Schlegel, Alice
  - Schlesinger, Edward R.
  - Schlesinger, Frank *
  - Schlesinger, George *
  - Schlesinger, Thomas (Dr.)
  - Schlichtig, Robert *
  - Schlom, Darrell G.
  - Schlor, Wolfgang
  - Schlosser, Duane
  - Schluchter, Wolfgang
  - Schmidt, Adolph
  - Schmidt, Amanda
  - Schmidt, David
  - Schmidt, Joe
  - Schmidt, Oswald *
  - Schmidt, Robert *
  - Schmidt, Victor
  - Schmitt, Gladys
  - Schmitt, Gladys (oversize) *
  - Schmitt, Herman L.
  - Schmitz, Herman J. *
  - Schneewind, Jerome *
  - Scheider, Arthur J.
  - Schneider, Chris
  - Schneider, Jeffrey
  - Schneider, Justin
  - Schneider, Walter K.
  - Schoen, Robert E.
  - Schoenberger, Harold W. *
  - Schofield, Janet
  - Schold, Clifford
  - Scholinksi, Daphne
  - Schomburg, Roberta
  - Schor, Ninaf
  - Schor, Robert
  - Schorr, Thomas
  - Schottenheimer, Marty *
  - Schrader, Otto H.
  - Schrading, Paul E. "Wesley" (Rev.)
  - Schram, Ivy Valerie
  - Schramm, Gustav L.
  - Schraut, Wolfgang H.
  - Schrobel, Charles W.
  - Schroedel, Dale P.
  - Schubert, Jack
  - Schubert, Mary Rogers
  - Schuchert, Joseph S. *
  - Schuck, Robert F.
  - Schuit, Kenneth E.
  - Schulhof, Katrina
  - Schulhof, Samuel A.
  - Schulman, Irwin J.
  - Schulte, Shane
  - Schulte, Wolfgang
  - Schulte-Ladbeck, Regina
  - Schultz, Jane S.
  - Schultz, Jerome
  - Schultz, John
  - Schultz, Randall L. *
  - Schultz, Richard
  - Schultz, Robert A.
  - Schultz, Ronald G.
  - Schultz, Scott
  - Schultz, Stanley (Dr.)
  - Schultz, William F., Jr.
  - Schultze, M. O.
  - Schulz, Richard
  - Schulz, William F., Jr.
  - Schumacher, Carolyn
  - Schumacher, David *
  - Schumacher, Sheila
  - Schuman, Joel S.
  - Schumann, Jack
  - Schunn, Christian
  - Schuster, Gerald
  - Schuthof, Katrina Veeder
  - Schwartz, Andrew
  - Schwartz, Donald M. *
  - Schwartz, Jeffrey
  - Schwartz, Mark
  - Schwartz, Meyer
  - Schwartz, Meyer "Mike" *
  - Schwartz, Michael
  - Schwartz, Myles
  - Schwartz, Richard
  - Schwartz, Rowena
  - Schwartz, Ruth
  - Schwartze, E. W.
  - Schwartzman, David
  - Schweinsberg, Harriet D. *
  - Schwentker, Frederic N. *
  - Schwerha, Joseph
  - Schwinghammer, Terry L.
  - Scia-Iabba, Mary Ann
  - Sciotti, Leslie Smedley
  - Scipio, Albert L., III (Dr.) *
  - Sciulli, Dominick C., Jr.
  - Sciulli, Victor
  - Sciullo, Peter A.
  - Sciullo, Sam
  - Sciurba, Frank
  - Sclabassi, Robert
  - Scopes, U. T.
  - Scott, Charles P. *
  - Scott, George Alvin
  - Scott, Horace C.
  - Scott, Reginald
  - Scott, Renee H.
  - Scott, Z. R.
  - Scovel, Charles W.
  - Scovel, Thomas *
  - Scranton, Ryan
  - Scranton, William *
  - Scribner, Henry
  - Scull, John I. *
  - Scully, Charles B. (class of 1837)
  - Scully, Jane, Sr.
  - Scully, John Pendleton
  - Scully, Rosemary
  - Seaberger, Richard (Dr.)
  - Seabrooks, Chris
  - Seal, Arlene B.
  - Seale, Bobby
  - Seals, Barbara
  - Searcy, William
  - Seavy, Julia M.
  - Sebak, Rick
  - Sebastian, Edward
  - Seckinger, Richard K.
  - Sedlar, Jean
  - Seddon, Johanna
  - Seehausen, Janet
  - Seelman, Katherine D.
  - Seels, Barbara
  - Sefranck, Helmut
  - Segal, Alan H.
  - Segal, David P. *
  - Segall, Bernard W. (Dr.)
  - Segel, Elizabeth
  - Segvic, Heda
  - Seidensticker, William D.
  - Seidman, John
  - Seif, Said M.
  - Seifert, Ray *
  - Seigle, Mark
  - Seiter, Milton S.
  - Seitz, James
  - Selavan, Ida Cohen
  - Seldin, Joseph E.
  - Seligman, Milton
  - Seligman, Sidney
  - Seligson, Mitchell A.
  - Sell, Stewart
  - Sell, W. Edward *
  - Sellars, Wilfrid *
  - Sellers, Robert Emory
  - Sellin, Leona G.
  - Seltser, Raymond (oversize) *
  - Selva, Paul J. (Major General)
  - Selwyn, Laine
  - Semenow, Robert W.
  - Semple, James S. *
  - Sepulveda, Ofelia Perez
  - Serafica, Felicisima
  - Sereika, Susan
  - Service, Kenneth P.
  - Sesack, Susan R.
  - Sessa, Frank *
  - Sewell, Deshaun
  - Seybert, Amy L.
  - Seydel, Rudigen V.
  - Seyler, William C.*
  - Seymour, Charles (Dr.)
  - Seznec, Jean J. (Dr.) *
  - Shabatura, Shirley
  - Shackle, G. L. S. (Dr.)
  - Shadduck, Richard K. *
  - Shafer, John Douglas *
  - Shafer, Lea A.
  - Shafer, Raymond *
  - Shaffer, Lowell
  - Shafritz, Jay
  - Shah, Yatish T. *
  - Shalbrack, Erin
  - Shaler, Robert C. *
  - Shallenberger, Dorothy
  - Shames, George (oversize)
  - Shames, Sally Oleon *
  - Shanghag, Arun S.
  - Shane, Allan C.
  - Shane, Peter
  - Shaner, James
  - Shankar, Ravi
  - Shannon, R. *
  - Shapira, Frieda
  - Shapiro, Alvin (oversize) *
  - Shapiro, Gerald M.
  - Shapiro, Gilbert
  - Shapiro, Maurice *
  - Shapiro, Moishe
  - Shapiro, Ronald
  - Share, Andrea
  - Sharif, Shona
  - Sharify, Nasser *
  - Sharkey, Andrew C.
  - Sharkey, Andrew G. "Jack"
  - Sharma, Ravi
  - Shattuck, Leroy J.
  - Shattuck, Leroy, Jr. (oversize) *
  - Shaver, James A.
  - Shaw, Daniel
  - Shaw, Jane *
  - Shaw, Pamela *
  - Shaw, Thomas Telson
  - Shaw-Stiffel, Thomas A. W.
  - Shea, Frank
  - Sheao-Hung, Chaing
  - Shear, M. Katherine
  - Sheehan, Robert
  - Sheeran, F. B.
  - Sheffler, Jack
  - Shefler, Laura
  - Shehorn, Patricia
  - Sheldon, R. E.
  - Shelkrot, Elliott L. *
  - Shelnutt, Eve
  - Shelton, Lawrence G.
  - Shelton, Whitford H.
  - Shen, Gary Gnixiong
  - Shen, George C.
  - Shenkan, Mark
  - Sheon, Aaron
  - Shepard, Judy
  - Shepard, Paul
  - Shepherd, Rex
  - Sheppard, C. C.
  - Sheps, Cecil G.
  - Sheps, Mindel
  - Sheptak, Peter E.
  - Sherman, Frank E. & Louise S.
  - Sherman, Herbert L. *
  - Sherman, Michael *
  - Sherman, William O'Neil *
  - Sherrill, Jackie (oversize) *
  - Sherrill, Richard Ellis *
  - Sherwood, Paul M. *
  - Shestak, Kenneth C.
  - Sheth, Jagdish
  - Shewe, Joseph
  - Shiarella, George R. *
  - Shibata, Katrina
  - Shibata, Ritei
  - Shibli, Khalid
  - Shield, Richard T.
  - Shields, Leet (oversize) *
  - Shields, William
  - Shiele, Donald L.
  - Shiffman, Saul
  - Shilling, Jack
  - Shiloh, Ailon
  - Shin, Doug Moon
  - Shin, Jumi
  - Shindell, Sidney *
  - Shiono, Rycnosuke (Dr.)
  - Shirer, John W.
  - Shirey, Donald *
  - Shirk, Jeneatte *
  - Shively, Jennifer
  - Shively, Stanley E. *
  - Shoben, Edward J. *
  - Shocker, Allan D. *
  - Shockley, Frank W. *
  - Shoener, Nicole
  - Shoenberg, David
  - Shoen, Aaron
  - Shooer, Bob
  - Shore, Barbara K. *
  - Shorr, Lori
  - Short, John A.
  - Shortliffe, Ernest (Dr.)
  - Shostak, Stanley
  - Shoub, Earle P.
  - Shoup, Melanie
  - Shrager, Jeff
  - Shragin, Boris
  - Shriver, Kathy
  - Shull, Kenneth H.
  - Shulman, Stuart W.
  - Shulte-Ladbeck, Regina
  - Shuman, Larry
  - Shumate, Roger V.
  - Shurin, Michael
  - Shuster, Brad
  - Shuster, E. *
  - Shuster, Gerald R.
  - Shusterman, Vladimir
  - Sianni, Jordan
  - Sibbet, Lorraine
  - Sibile, Etienne
  - Sica, Paul A.
  - Sidel, Philip
  - Sidhu, Surian S. *
  - Sieber, P. R.
  - Sieber, Roy (Dr.)
  - Siedle, Theodore
  - Sieg, Lee Paul *
  - Siegel, Edwin R.
  - Siegel, Jacob P. (Dr.)
  - Siegel, Michael I. (Dr.)
  - Siegel, Naomi *
  - Siegfried, Jill
  - Sierawski, Clare S.
  - Siew, Shirley
  - Siewers, Ralph D. *
  - Sigal, Alex
  - Sigmund, Thomas F.
  - Sikora, Marion
  - Sikora, Mark
  - Silberblatt, Gloria
  - Siler, Steve
  - Sillman, Deborah
  - Silbaggio, Vince
  - Silver, David
  - Silver, Edward A.
  - Silverman, Alexander
  - Silverman, Arnold B.
  - Silverman, Gary A.
  - Silverman, Joseph S. (Dr.)
  - Silverman, Margarita
  - Silverman, Melissa
  - Silverman, Myrna
  - Silverman, Robert (Dr.)
  - Silvestre, Anthony
  - Simann, Marwan A.
  - Simerly, Calvin
  - Simhan, Hyagriv
  - Siminerio, Linda M.
  - Simmons, George *
  - Simmons, Richard L.
  - Simmons, Richard P.
  - Simmons, Roberta Grodberg
  - Simmons, Russell
  - Simmonds, James *
  - Simms, Shawn
  - Simon, Connie
  - Simon, Herbert A.
  - Simon, Marc A.
  - Simon, Roger
  - Simons, Daniel J. *
  - Simonson, Peter
  - Simonton, Thomas Grier *
  - Simpson, Chandra
  - Sims, Adolph
  - Sims, Harold
  - Sims, Kenneth
  - Sims, Patsy
  - Simes, Wayne U.
  - Sindhi, Rakesh
  - Singer, Marshall (Dr.)
  - Singh, Chandralekha
  - Singh, Balwant (Dr.)
  - Singh, Shivendra
  - Singh, Vijai
  - Singleton, John
  - Singleton, Rebecca
  - Singleton, Roslyn
  - Siocchetti, Lauren
  - Siporin, Rae *
  - Sipp, Warren
  - Sipple, H. L.
  - Siribanpitak, Pruet
  - Siska, Peter E. *
  - Sissman, Isaac (Dr.)
  - Sisterson, Douglas G.
  - Sites, Edward W. *
  - Siuda, Kathy
  - Sizemore, Barbara
  - Skewis, Savina (oversize) *
  - Skladany, Joe
  - Skledar, Susan J.
  - Skolnick, Leon
  - Skrabut, Myron *
  - Skrzycki, Cindy
  - Skuta, Philip
  - Skutsch, Otto
  - Slack, Edward J.
  - Slade, Lamarr
  - Sladen, Arnold, MD *
  - Slater, Frank
  - Slater, Robert
  - Slatkes, Leonard J. (Dr.)
  - Slaughter, Kyle
  - Slaughter, William S.
  - Slavik, Juray (Dr.)
  - Slawson, A. Wayne (Dr.)
  - Sleasman, David
  - Slesinger, Reuben (oversize) *
  - Slevin, Dennis P. (Dr.) *
  - Sleznak, Lester
  - Slicer, Deborah
  - Slife, Richard D. (Major)
  - Slivka, Adam
  - Slone, Tom
  - Sloss, John H.
  - Sluk, John *
  - Small, Charles
  - Small, Norman C.
  - Smalley, Ruth *
  - Smeltz, Aurelia
  - Smetanka, Stella
  - Smethurst, Mae J. (Dr.)
  - Smiach, Deborah
  - Smialek, Kenneth
  - Smith, Albert B.
  - Smith, Albert E.
  - Smith, Albert G.
  - Smith, Alice
  - Smith, Andy
  - Smith, Bob
  - Smith, Cory
  - Smith, Curtis
  - Smith, Daniel *
  - Smith, David *
  - Smith, Deborah Ann
  - Smith, Don
  - Smith, Donald Hugh *
  - Smith, Donna *
  - Smith, Edgar F.
  - Smith, Gregory
  - Smith, Gretta
  - Smith, Griffith *
  - Smith, Herbert C.
  - Smith, J. William *
  - Smith, James (Colonel)
  - Smith, Jan D.
  - Smith, Jane *
  - Smith, John Robert *
  - Smith, John Selmer *
  - Smith, John Thomas, Jr. *
  - Smith, Joshua I.
  - Smith, Kenneth
  - Smith, Kimball
  - Smith, Margaret
  - Smith, Mathilda Hudson *
  - Smith, Namosha Joni K.
  - Smith, Perry
  - Smith, Philip
  - Smith, R. B. *
  - Smith, Raymond W.
  - Smith, Rhoten A. (oversize) *
  - Smith, Robert McNeil
  - Smith, Roland
  - Smith, Sharon P.
  - Smith, Stephen
  - Smith, Susan Harris
  - Smith, Terence
  - Smith, Trecia
  - Smith, Vivienne
  - Smith, William K.
  - Smither, Ethel L.
  - Smithers, Michael *
  - Smithgall, Thomas
  - Smokelin, Jennifer
  - Smole, William (Dr.)
  - Smolinski, Patrick
  - Smookler, Harold
  - Smudski, James
  - Smyers, Burt H.
  - Smyers, E. C.
  - Smyth, Henry F.
  - Snead, James
  - Snitger, Kara
  - Snodgrass, W. D.
  - Snoke, David
  - Snook, Theodore
  - Snow, Robert *
  - Snowden, John M. *
  - Snowden, Roy R. (Dr.)
  - Snyder, Gerald J.
  - Snyder, Joan
  - Snyder, Keith S.
  - Snyder, Neil R.
  - Snyder, Richard
  - Snyder, William P. *
  - Snyderman, Carl H.
  - Soares, Jair C.
  - Sobal, David
  - Sobotka, Walter *
  - Sobejano, Gonzalo
  - Sobel, Albert E. (Dr.)
  - Sobol, Robert W.
  - Sochatoff, Belle *
  - Sochats, Kenneth
  - Soderbergh, Peter *
  - Soergel, Kenneth
  - Soffa, Mary Louise
  - Soffa, William H.
  - Soffel, Sara M. *
  - Soliman, Ibrahim
  - Solinger, Dorothy
  - Sollecito, William A.
  - Solodar, Henry Allan
  - Soloman, Andrew
  - Solomon, Zelda
  - Solon, Jerry A.
  - Solow, Anatole A.
  - Soltis, Victoria
  - Solyan, Paul
  - Somers, R. E.
  - Sommer, Marc
  - Somogyi, Dan
  - Sonbolian, Nasser *
  - Sonel, Ali F.
  - Sones, Warren *
  - Songer, Dan
  - Songer, Thomas J.
  - Sonis, M. (Dr.) *
  - Sonneman, George
  - Soo-Song, Lee
  - Soran, Z. Ozlem
  - Sorber, Charles *
  - Soriano, David
  - Soros, George
  - Sota, Julius
  - Souder, William E.
  - South, Dorothy Jean
  - South-Paul, Jeannette
  - Southers, Mark
  - Southworth, Horton C.
  - Sowande, Fela
  - Spamer, Bryan
  - Spangler, David Sheridan
  - Sparkes, Harry
  - Sparto, Patrick
  - Sparvero, Louis J.
  - Spates, David
  - Spatz, Sidney
  - Spaulding, James
  - Spaulding, Seth *
  - Spear, Richard D. (Dr.)
  - Spectar, Jem
  - Specter, Arlen
  - Specter, Edward
  - Spector, Calvin
  - Spector, Gerald J. *
  - Speer, Alexander M.
  - Speer, James R. (Dr.) *
  - Speer, William
  - Speers, Rex W. (Dr.)
  - Speller, J. Finton (Dr.)
  - Spence, Robert
  - Spencer, Darnell
  - Spencer, Herbert L. *
  - Spencer, Shawntae
  - Sperling, Mark A.
  - Sperner, Emanuel *
  - Spice, Gordon (Dr.)
  - Spicer, Gregory A.
  - Spicher, Charlotte Mae
  - Spiegelman, Barbara
  - Spier, Barbara Elliott
  - Spiess, Eliot B. *
  - Spigel, Irwin (Dr.)
  - Spingarn, Karl
  - Spink, Amanda
  - Spires, Dewayne A.
  - Spiro, Michael H. *
  - Spisak, Daniel
  - Spitz, Kathryn
  - Spivak, Gayatri
  - Spock, Benjamin
  - Spoehr, Alexander *
  - Spore, Mary Beth
  - Sposato, Jeffrey S.
  - Sprague, Carol S.
  - Spring, Michael
  - Springer, Cecile M.
  - Springer, Eric *
  - Sproull, John Wallace
  - Sproull, Thomas (Rev.) *
  - Sridharan, U. C.
  - Srivastava, Sanjay K.
  - Srun, H. H. (oversize)
  - Stabile, Laura
  - Stace, Walter T.
  - Stacey, Frank Donald (Dr.)
  - Stachel, John
  - Stadin, Jonathan
  - Stadlin, Jon
  - Stafford, Robert L.
  - Stagg, Vaughn
  - Stahl, David *
  - Stahl, Hans Peter
  - Stahr, Elvis J. *
  - Staley, Robert
  - Stalley, Marshall
  - Stallman, Richard
  - Stanchina, William
  - Staniland, Albert E.
  - Staniland, Martin
  - Stankard, Helen *
  - Stank, Ronald (Dr.)
  - Stanley, James T.
  - Stanley, William
  - Stanton, William (Dr.)
  - Star, Alex
  - Staresiic, Nick J.
  - Staresinich, Craig
  - Stark, John (Rev.) (class of 1824)
  - Stark, Karl J.
  - Stark, Lucille
  - Stark, Nathan J. *
  - Stark, Shirley *
  - Starks, Esther B.
  - Starnes, Leland *
  - Starrett, Agnes Lynch (oversize) *
  - Starrett, C. V. *
  - Starz, Terrance W.
  - Starzenski, Gene
  - Starzl, Joy
  - Starzl, Thomas (oversize) *
  - Stasiak, Edward M.
  - States, Stanley
  - Steadman, Charles W. *
  - Stebbins, Harold
  - Steed, David L.
  - Steel, Gardner
  - Steel, Gardner (oversize)
  - Steele, Logan H.
  - Steele, Ray
  - Steele, Robert
  - Steele, Susan A.
  - Steele, William A.
  - Steers, Stanley
  - Steets, Jannette A.
  - Stefancic, Jean
  - Stefanovic-Racic, M.
  - Stefanski, Eric
  - Stegeman, Gebhard
  - Stehle, Philip
  - Steichen, Felicien
  - Stein, Felix
  - Stein, Herbert
  - Stein, John
  - Stein, Josh
  - Stein, Mary Kay
  - Stein, Sharon
  - Stein, Sylvan (Mrs.) (oversize) *
  - Stein, Tim
  - Steinberg, William
  - Steiner, Wendy
  - Steinke, Edith
  - Stelter, Charles J.
  - Stemke, Gerald W.
  - Stendahl, Kister (Dr.)
  - Stenger, V. Andrew
  - Stenson, Kiernan F.
  - Stepanovich, G.
  - Stephens, Lemuel *
  - Stephens, Norris *
  - Stephens, Thomas M.
  - Stephenson, Richard *
  - Stephenson, W. A.
  - Stepnoski, Mark
  - Sternberg, Virginia
  - Sterne, Colin *
  - Sternfeld, Frederick W. (Dr.)
  - Sternfield, (Prof.) *
  - Sternglass, Ernest
  - Stetten, George
  - Stevens, Charles L. (Dr.)
  - Stevens, Godfrey D. *
  - Stevenson, Edward K.
  - Stevenson, George
  - Stevenson, John D.
  - Stevenson, Mark
  - Stewart, Alec
  - Stewart, Alison
  - Stewart, Andrew F.
  - Stewart, Barbara
  - Stewart, Brooke
  - Stewart, Doris Simpson
  - Stewart, Edward C.
  - Stewart, E. Duane
  - Stewart, Ella P. Myers *
  - Stewart, George M.
  - Stewart, George W.
  - Stewart, Glenn Alexander
  - Stewart, Hamilton
  - Stewart, Kenneth *
  - Stewart, Kordell
  - Stewart, Marjory
  - Stewart, Mervin
  - Stewart, Pamela
  - Stewart, R. J. *
  - Stewart, Reid T. (oversize) *
  - Stewart, Ronald
  - Stewart, Ruth Ann
  - Stiber, Andre C. *
  - Stickel, Harold S. "Hap"
  - Stickler, Daniel
  - Stieman, Paul
  - Stiff, Robert H. *
  - Stiles, Megan
  - Stiger, Richard P.
  - Stiller, Richard L. *
  - Stilley, Carol
  - Stilley, Lori
  - Stilwell, David
  - Stinehcomb, James
  - Stine, Dan
  - Stineberg, Warren (Dr.)
  - Stinson, George A.
  - Stitt, Nancy
  - Stock, Aaron Hirsh
  - Stock, Maryanne F.
  - Stock, Richard (Dr.)
  - Stocks, Janet
  - Stockton, Joseph *
  - Stoddart, J. Fraser
  - Stoecklein, Christian
  - Stoehr, Gary
  - Stoffer, David S.
  - Stojanovic, Svetozar
  - Stone, C. Walter *
  - Stone, Daniel
  - Stone, David
  - Stone, Donald C. *
  - Stone, E. C.
  - Stone, Joe
  - Stone, John T.
  - Stoneley, Robert
  - Stones, M. Alison
  - Stophlet, Donald V. *
  - Stottlemyer, Rande
  - Stotz, Carl L. (oversize) *
  - Stotz, Elmer H.
  - Stout, Charles D.